Guide to the Thornton Wilder Papers
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Correspondence, 1908-1985; Series I; 27.11; (67 boxes)
  - GENERAL CORRESPONDENCE
    - Kiel University English Seminar, 1963 (Box 45, Folder 1169)
      See also: Klaüs Hausmann, Box 41, folder 1033
    - Kilty, Jerome, 1961-69, n.d. (Box 45, Folder 1170)
    - Kingsbury, Stanley, 1966-69, n.d. (Box 45, Folder 1171)
    - Kingsbury, Eileen
      With: notes on Kingsbury genealogy and letters to and from Isabel Wilder on Kingsbury and Amos Parker Wilder
    - Kinsey, Alfred C., 1950 Jan 26 (Box 45, Folder 1172)
    - Kirkpatrick, Ralph, 1973 Nov 24 (Box 45, Folder 1173)
    - Kissinger, Henry A., 1962-63 (Box 45, Folder 1174)
    - Klein, Arthur, 1951 (Box 45, Folder 1175)
    - Klemperer, Otto, 1960-75 (Box 45, Folder 1176)
    - Klemperer, Lotte
    - Knowles, John, 1956 Apr 6 (Box 45, Folder 1177)
    - KNXT Television, 1963 (Box 45, Folder 1178)
    - Koepf, John, 1962 Apr 24 (Box 45, Folder 1179)
      With: pencil sketches by Koepf of Southwest scenes
    - Köhn, Horst, 1966 (Box 45, Folder 1180)
    - Konopka, Gisela, 1962 (Box 45, Folder 1181)
    - Kozelka, Paul, 1959 (Box 45, Folder 1182)
    - Kubanek, Marion D., 1962-65 (Box 45, Folder 1183)
    - "L" general, [1927]-75, n.d. (Box 45, Folder 1184-1187)
    - L. W. Singer, 1955-64 (Box 45, Folder 1188)
    - La Guardia, Fiorello, 1944 Jan 17 (Box 45, Folder 1189)
    - Laidlaw Brothers, 1961 (Box 45, Folder 1190)
    - Land, Donald, 1963, n.d. (Box 45, Folder 1191)
    - Lane, Ruth, 1962, n.d. (Box 45, Folder 1192)
    - Laserna Pinzon, Mario, 1956-75 (Box 45, Folder 1193)
    - Lasswell, Clyde, 1953-66, n.d. (Box 45, Folder 1194)
    - Lasswell, Mary, 1953-67, n.d. (Box 45, Folder 1195)
    - Laughlin, James, 1975 Oct 7 (Box 45, Folder 1196)
      See also: New Directions, Box 50, folder 1358
    - Lavery, Emmet, 1938-70 (Box 45, Folder 1197)
      Includes photocopy of article, "Agreement at Midnight"
    - Lawrenceville School, 1963-67 (Box 45, Folder 1198)
    - Layton, William, 1939-82, n.d. (Box 45, Folder 1199-1200)
    - Léger, Alexis
      See: Saint-John Perse, Box 54, folder 1497
    - LeGrand, Julian and family, 1948-74, n.d. (Box 45, Folder 1201-1202)
      With: wedding vows of Julian LeGrand
    - Lehr, Wilson, 1939-73, n.d. (Box 45, Folder 1203-1205)
    - Leigh, Vivien, 1944-60, n.d. (Box 45, Folder 1206-1207)
      See also: Sir Laurence Olivier, Box 50, folder 1376-1377
    - Leighton, Alice, 1918-19, n.d. (Box 46, Folder 1208)
    - Leighton, Constance May, 1950 (Box 46, Folder 1209)
    - Lesser, Hal, 1961-69 (Box 46, Folder 1210)
    - Lesser, Sol, 1939-75, n.d. (Box 46, Folder 1211-1216)
    - Levi, Edward H., 1963-71 (Box 46, Folder 1217)
    - Levin, Calman A, 1967 (Box 46, Folder 1218)
    - Levin, Meyer, 1959, n.d. (Box 46, Folder 1219)
    - Levy, Murray, 1963 (Box 46, Folder 1220)
    - Lewis, Sinclair, 1938 Mar 16 (Box 46, Folder 1221)
    - Lewis, Wilmarth ("Lefty"), 1958-76, n.d. (Box 46, Folder 1222)
    - Leyda, Jay, 1969-74, n.d. (Box 46, Folder 1223)
    - Libraphone, 1959 (Box 46, Folder 1224)
    - Library and Museum of the Performing Arts, 1966-74 (Box 46, Folder 1225)
    - Library of Congress, 1942-69 (Box 46, Folder 1226)
      Includes copyright registration for The Skin of Our Teeth, 1942 Mar 24
    - Liebert, Herman W., 1967 Apr 9 (Box 46, Folder 1227)
    - Life, 1965-66 (Box 46, Folder 1228)
    - Lightfoot, Margaret, 1962 (Box 46, Folder 1229)
    - Lillie, Ralph, 1939, n.d. (Box 46, Folder 1229a)
      With other Lillie family letters, 1975, n.d.
    - The Limited Editions Club, 1939-75 (Box 46, Folder 1230)
    - Lincoln Center for the Performing Arts, 1963-67, n.d. (Box 46, Folder 1231)
    - Linder, Erich, 1953-71 (Box 46, Folder 1232)
    - Lindsay, Howard, 1962-63 (Box 46, Folder 1233)
    - Lindtberg, Leopold, 1957, n.d. (Box 46, Folder 1234)
    - Little, Brown & Co., 1964-75 (Box 46, Folder 1235)
    - Littman, Mark, 1968-71 (Box 46, Folder 1236)
    - Locher, David, 1964-68 (Box 46, Folder 1237)
      With: "Thornton Wilder's Bridge" by Locher
    - Lohmann, Carl E., 1934 May 14 (Box 46, Folder 1238)
    - Longford, Christine, 1941-46, n.d. (Box 46, Folder 1239)
    - Longman, Mark
      See: Longmans, Green & Co. Limited, Box 46, folders 1240-1245
    - Longman, R. G.
    - Longmans, Green & Co. Limited, 1929-59 (Box 46, Folder 1240-1243)
      Includes third-party correspondence concerning British publication rights
    - Longmans, Green & Co. Limited, 1960-74, n.d. (Box 47, Folder 1244-1245)
    - Loomis, Kenyon, 1965 (Box 47, Folder 1246)
    - Loos, Anita, 1962, 1963 (Box 47, Folder 1247)
    - Los Angeles Civic Light Opera, 1965 (Box 47, Folder 1248)
    - Lowe, Charles, n.d. (Box 47, Folder 1249)
    - Loyd, A. Dennis, 1966-82, n.d. (Box 47, Folder 1250-1251)
    - Luce, Claire Boothe, 1967, n.d. (Box 47, Folder 1252)
    - Luce, Henry R., 1926-56 (Box 47, Folder 1253)
    - Luetge, William, 1964-66 (Box 47, Folder 1254)
    - Luhan, Mabel Dodge, 1929-38, n.d. (Box 47, Folder 1255-1256)
      See also: Box 210, folder 4434
    - Lundbergh, Holger, 1956-59 (Box 47, Folder 1257)
    - Lunt, Alfred, 1937-46, n.d. (Box 47, Folder 1258)
    - Fontanne, Lynn
    - Lyons, Leonard, 1962-64 (Box 47, Folder 1259)
      With: copy of letter to Lyons from Sean O'Casey, 1962 Mar 20
    - "M" general, 1912-75, n.d. (Box 47, Folder 1260-1264)
    - McAfee, Helen, 1942, 1953 (Box 47, Folder 1265)
    - McCasland, Elizabeth Barron, 1952-72 (Box 48, Folder 1266)
    - McClain, Louise, 1963, n.d. (Box 48, Folder 1267)
    - McDaniel, Walton Brooks, 1973 Oct 8 (Box 48, Folder 1268)
    - MacDiarmid, Hugh, 1955 Aug 25 (Box 48, Folder 1269)
    - McDowall, Roddy, 1965, n.d. (Box 48, Folder 1270)
    - MacDowell Colony, 1925-73, n.d. (Box 48, Folder 1271)
    - McElfresh, Earl, 1966 (Box 48, Folder 1272)
    - McGinley, Phyllis, 1965, 1967 (Box 48, Folder 1273)
    - McGinnis, Hugh, 1962-63 (Box 48, Folder 1274)
    - McGraw-Hill Book Company, Inc., 1962-72 (Box 48, Folder 1275)
    - McGrory, Mary, 1968 Dec 22 (Box 48, Folder 1276)
    - McKellar, Donald C.
      See: Greenwood Little Theater, Box 36, folder 933
    - MacLiammoir, Micheal, 1951 Apr 14 (Box 48, Folder 1277)
    - MacLeish, Archibald, 1945-46, n.d. (Box 48, Folder 1278)
    - Macmillan Co., 1954-62 (Box 48, Folder 1279)
    - McNally, Terence, 1965, n.d. (Box 48, Folder 1280)
    - Mahood, Richard, 1966 (Box 48, Folder 1281)
    - Malone, Kemp, 1967 (Box 48, Folder 1282)
    - Maniatis, Phyllis, 1964-70 (Box 48, Folder 1283)
    - Mann, Theodore, 1959-64 (Box 48, Folder 1284)
    - Mahler, Alma, 1953-57 (Box 48, Folder 1285)
    - Mantell, Harold, 1962-77, n.d. (Box 48, Folder 1286-1287)
    - Mantzke, Martin, 1962-66 (Box 48, Folder 1288)
    - March, Florence, 1943, n.d. (Box 48, Folder 1289)
    - March, Reginald, [1920s] (Box 48, Folder 1290)
    - Mark Twain Journal
      See: Cyril Clemens, Box 29, folder 691
    - Martin, Mary, 1953-75, n.d. (Box 48, Folder 1291)
    - Marton, Elizabeth, 1953-72 (Box 48, Folder 1292)
    - Mason, Lawrence, 1918, n.d. (Box 48, Folder 1293)
    - Massey, Raymond, 1945-79 (Box 48, Folder 1294)
    - Mathews, Carmen, 1962 (Box 48, Folder 1295)
    - Matthews, Jack, 1964-65 (Box 48, Folder 1296)
    - Mattray, Maria, 1944 (Box 48, Folder 1297)
    - Mauclair, Anny, 1959-65 (Box 48, Folder 1298-1299)
    - Maugham, W. Somerset, 1961 Feb 1 (Box 48, Folder 1300)
    - Maurri, Maria, 1962 (Box 48, Folder 1301)
    - Maxwell, Robert, 1944 (Box 48, Folder 1302)
    - Mayer, William R., 1964 (Box 48, Folder 1303)
    - Meekins, Mel, 1970 (Box 48, Folder 1304)
    - Mendelssohn, Eleonora, 1935, n.d. (Box 48, Folder 1305)
    - Menotti, Gian Carlo, 1963 (Box 48, Folder 1306)
    - Merande, Doro, 1942, 1968, n.d. (Box 48, Folder 1307)
    - Meredith Press, 1967 (Box 48, Folder 1308)
    - Merlini, Elsa, 1952-81, n.d. (Box 48, Folder 1309)
    - Merrick, David, 1955-71, n.d. (Box 48, Folder 1310)
    - Merriman, Dan, 1950-62, n.d. (Box 48, Folder 1311)
    - Meryman, Richard
      See: Life, Box 46, folder 1228
    - Metcalfe, Addison, 1953-57 (Box 48, Folder 1312)
    - Metzdorf, Robert F., 1962 (Box 48, Folder 1313)
    - Meyerowitz, Patricia, 1967-71 (Box 48, Folder 1314)
    - Michaels, Kurt, 1947-48 (Box 48, Folder 1315)
    - Mickel, Liselotte, 1966-70 (Box 49, Folder 1316)
      With: "Thornton Wilder und der americkanische Optimismus," in Frankfurter Hefte, 1969 Dec
    - Milosz, Czeslaw, 1947 May 23 (Box 49, Folder 1317)
    - Milwaukee Repertory Theatre, 1968 (Box 49, Folder 1318)
    - Miner, Earl Roy, 1953 Jul 10 (Box 49, Folder 1319)
    - Miner, Worthington, 1963 (Box 49, Folder 1320)
    - Minnesota Theater Company, 1965-67 (Box 49, Folder 1321)
    - Mitchell, Jean Fair, 1950-51 (Box 49, Folder 1322)
    - Mitgang, Herbert, 1965-66 (Box 49, Folder 1323)
    - Mix, Katherine L., 1962-65 (Box 49, Folder 1324)
    - Modern Language Association, 1963-66 (Box 49, Folder 1325)
    - Moiseiwitsch, Tanya, 1963-76, n.d. (Box 49, Folder 1326)
    - Montgomery County Board of Education, 1961 (Box 49, Folder 1327)
    - Moore, Harry T., 1963-67 (Box 49, Folder 1328)
    - Morgan, Frederick
      See: Hudson Review, Box 43, folder 1112
    - Morley, Griswold, 1949-70 (Box 49, Folder 1329)
    - Morrell, Ottoline, Lady, 1939 Jan 17 (Box 49, Folder 1330)
    - Morris Theatre Foundation, 1966 (Box 49, Folder 1331)
    - Motatch, Joyce, 1964-65 (Box 49, Folder 1332)
    - Motif, 1960 (Box 49, Folder 1333)
    - Mount Holyoke College, 1962-63 (Box 49, Folder 1334)
    - Mudgett, Harold, Mrs., 1928 (Box 49, Folder 1335)
    - Müller, Otto, 1940-70 (Box 49, Folder 1336)
    - Murphy, Gerald, 1945 Aug 8 (Box 49, Folder 1337)
    - Musmanno, M. A., 1940 Aug 22 (Box 49, Folder 1338)
    - Myerberg, Michael, 1938-71, n.d. (Box 49, Folder 1339-1341)
    - "N" general, 1930-75, n.d. (Box 49, Folder 1342-1344)
    - Nagy, Elemer, 1962-63 (Box 49, Folder 1345)
    - Nardi, Marcia, 1952-56, n.d. (Box 49, Folder 1346-1347)
      With: 2 letters to Wilder from John [Edmunds] and corrected typescripts of 2 groups of poems by Nardi
    - Nash, Sally, 1946 Jan, n.d. (Box 49, Folder 1348)
    - Nasman, Diana, 1966 (Box 49, Folder 1349)
    - National Broadcasting Company, Inc., 1956-68 (Box 49, Folder 1350)
    - National Council of Teachers of English, 1965 (Box 49, Folder 1351)
    - National Educational Television, 1963-66 (Box 49, Folder 1352)
    - National Institute of Arts and Letters
      See: Glenway Wescott, Box 62, folders 1718-1720
    - National Performing Arts, 1967-68 (Box 49, Folder 1353)
    - National Theatre Conference, 1963 (Box 49, Folder 1354)
    - Nelson, Eva Mudge, 1943 (Box 49, Folder 1355)
    - Nelson, Howard, 1963-66 (Box 50, Folder 1356)
    - New American Library, 1963-67 (Box 50, Folder 1357)
    - New Directions, 1952-67 (Box 50, Folder 1358)
      See also: James Laughlin, Box 45, folder 1196
    - New England Theatre Conference, 1966 (Box 50, Folder 1359)
    - New Hampshire Commission on the Arts, 1971 (Box 50, Folder 1360)
    - New York Public Library, 1938-66 (Box 50, Folder 1361)
      See also: George Freedley, Box 33, folder 856
    - Newberry, Samuel David, 1962 Jul 2 (Box 50, Folder 1362)
      With: prospectus for A Pound of Ezra
    - Newsweek, 1962-63 (Box 50, Folder 1363)
    - Newton, Charles, 1964-73 (Box 50, Folder 1364)
    - Noe, Henry M., 1967-73, n.d. (Box 50, Folder 1365)
    - Nolan-Yellin Productions, 1958-59 (Box 50, Folder 1366)
    - Nolen, Jody, 1974-76, n.d. (Box 50, Folder 1367)
      With: letter to Wilder from William Nolen, 1974
    - Nordoff, Paul, 1975, n.d. (Box 50, Folder 1368)
    - Northwestern University, 1962-65 (Box 50, Folder 1369)
    - Norton, Elliot, 1962 (Box 50, Folder 1370)
    - "O" general, 1939-75, n.d. (Box 50, Folder 1371)
    - O'Hara, John, 1965 Jan 17 (Box 50, Folder 1372)
    - Oenslager, Donald Mitchell, 1965-82 (Box 50, Folder 1373)
    - Ohm, August, 1964-65 (Box 50, Folder 1374)
    - Oliver, Edith, 1972-73 (Box 50, Folder 1375)
    - Olivier, Laurence, Sir, 1945-72, n.d. (Box 50, Folder 1376-77)
      See also: Vivien Leigh, Box 45, folders 1203-1204
    - Olney, Dorothy Olney, Julian
      See: National Performing Arts, Box 49, folder 1353
    - O'Neil, F. J., 1964-79 (Box 50, Folder 1378)
    - O'Neill, Eugene, 1940 Sep 29 (Box 50, Folder 1379)
    - [O'Neill?], James, 1954-75, n.d. (Box 50, Folder 1380)
    - Onyshkevych, Larissa, 1973 (Box 50, Folder 1381)
    - Orden pour le mérite, 1966, 1969 (Box 50, Folder 1382)
    - Orff, Carl, 1953 Mar 22 (Box 50, Folder 1383)
    - Osborn, Robert, 1972, n.d. (Box 50, Folder 1384)
    - Osborn, Elodie
    - Ostro, Ida, 1964, n.d. (Box 50, Folder 1385)
    - "Pa"-"Pe" general, 1925-75, n.d. (Box 50, Folder 1386-1388)
    - "Pi"-"Pu" general, 1938-75, n.d. (Box 51, Folder 1389-1390)
    - P. E. N., 1946-67 (Box 51, Folder 1390a)
    - Pace College, 1963 (Box 51, Folder 1391)
    - Packard, William, 1965-66 (Box 51, Folder 1392)
    - Pankhurst, [J. J.?], 1953-59 (Box 51, Folder 1393)
    - Parke-Bernet Galleries
      See: Robert F. Metzdorf, Box 48, folder 1313
    - Partridge, Eric, 1954, 1956 (Box 51, Folder 1394)
    - Partridge, Frances, 1962 (Box 51, Folder 1395)
    - Patchen, Kenneth, 1953 May 17 (Box 51, Folder 1396)
      With: inscription to Thornton Wilder, n.d.
    - Paul C. Richards Autographs, 1964 (Box 51, Folder 1397)
    - Paul, Peter, 1965, n.d. (Box 51, Folder 1398)
    - Paxton, Vincoe, 1951-53 (Box 51, Folder 1399)
    - Penfield, Thornton, 1967-68 (Box 51, Folder 1400)
    - Penguin Books, 1968 (Box 51, Folder 1401)
    - People-to-People Program, 1956-64, n.d. (Box 51, Folder 1402)
    - Perkins, Lawrence, 1967-68 (Box 51, Folder 1403)
    - Periera, Irene Rice, n.d. (Box 51, Folder 1404)
      With: drawing by Periera
    - Perogloy, Etta, 1921 (Box 51, Folder 1405)
    - Perry Common Comprehensive School, 1965 (Box 51, Folder 1406)
    - Perseus, 1963-64 (Box 51, Folder 1407)
    - Peter, Emmett B., Jr., 1963 (Box 51, Folder 1408)
    - Phelps, William Lyon, 1928-43, n.d. (Box 51, Folder 1409)
      With: invitation to address by Phelps to the Salvation Army Day Public Gathering, printed, n.d.
    - Phoenix Theatre, 1961-65 (Box 51, Folder 1410)
    - Phoenix Theatre, Leicester, 1963 (Box 51, Folder 1411)
    - Pickford, Mary, 1933, n.d. (Box 51, Folder 1412)
    - Pierson, George W., 1963 (Box 51, Folder 1413)
    - Pitts, Rebecca, 1964 (Box 51, Folder 1414)
    - Planned Parenthood, 1966 (Box 51, Folder 1415)
    - Platthy, Jenó, 1962-64 (Box 51, Folder 1416)
      With: typescript, signed of "Thornton Wilder"
    - Platzer, Wilifried
      See: Austria, Box 15, folder 349
    - The Players, 1962-66 (Box 51, Folder 1417)
    - The Playhouse, 1962-66 (Box 51, Folder 1418)
    - Pletzke-Baker Associates, Inc., 1965 (Box 51, Folder 1419)
    - Plowright, Joan, [1968] (Box 51, Folder 1420)
    - Pocket Books, Inc., 1947-68 (Box 51, Folder 1421)
    - The Poetry Center, 1964-65 (Box 51, Folder 1422)
    - Pollard, Terry, 1952 Dec 28 (Box 51, Folder 1423)
    - Popper, Hermine, 1964-65 (Box 51, Folder 1424)
      With: typescript carbon of "The Universe of Thornton Wilder" by Popper
    - Pound, Ezra, 1951 (Box 51, Folder 1425)
    - Pound, Dorothy
    - Powell, Emma Moody, 1963 (Box 51, Folder 1426)
    - Powell, Mel, 1975 Aug 19 (Box 51, Folder 1427)
      See also: Martha Scott, Box 55, folder 1526
    - Preminger, Marion, 1949-65 (Box 51, Folder 1428-1430)
      With: carbons of correspondence, reports and expense accounts relating to the Albert Schweitzer Hospital Fund, an advertisement for All I Want Is Everything, and a photocopy of Preminger's marriage license
    - Preminger, Otto, 1946 Nov 13 (Box 51, Folder 1431)
    - Previn, André, 1975 Jun 28 (Box 51, Folder 1432)
      See also: Mia Farrow, Box 33, folder 824-825
    - Prince, Diana Cochrane, 1973-74, n.d. (Box 52, Folder 1433)
    - Prince, Leslie, 1935-36 (Box 52, Folder 1434)
    - Princeton Alumni Association, 1962-65 (Box 52, Folder 1435)
    - Princeton University, 1962-67 (Box 52, Folder 1436)
    - Princeton University Press, 1955-65 (Box 52, Folder 1437)
    - Prokosch, Frederic, 1941-60, n.d. (Box 52, Folder 1438)
      With: inscribed copy of The Ghost City by Prokosch
    - The Providence Journal, 1967 (Box 52, Folder 1439)
    - Pulitzer Prize Advisory Board, 1966 (Box 52, Folder 1440)
    - Purdy, James, 1956 (Box 52, Folder 1441)
      With: inscribed title page of 63: Dream Palace
    - "Q" general, 1962-73 (Box 52, Folder 1442)
    - Quintero, José, 1957-75 (Box 52, Folder 1443)
      With: letter to Isabel Wilder signed "Cavada," 1975
    - "R" general, 1930-75, n.d. (Box 52, Folder 1444-1447)
    - Raffel, Gertrude Stein, 1959-65 (Box 52, Folder 1448)
    - Random House, Inc., 1962-75 (Box 52, Folder 1449)
    - Rathbone, Richard, 1927-38 (Box 52, Folder 1450)
    - Rattigan, Terrence, 1946-48, n.d. (Box 52, Folder 1451)
    - Reader's Digest, 1959-65 (Box 52, Folder 1452)
    - Reavey, George, 1953 (Box 52, Folder 1453)
      With: signed typescripts of 3 poems by Reavey
    - Redbook, 1953 (Box 52, Folder 1454)
    - Redfern, Richard, 1965-67 (Box 52, Folder 1455)
    - Redgrave, Michael, Sir, 1941-54, n.d. (Box 52, Folder 1456-1457)
    - Reed, Joseph Verner, 1963-64 (Box 52, Folder 1458)
    - Reed, Kit, 1975 (Box 52, Folder 1459)
      With: copy of review of Richard Goldstone's biography by Reed
    - Reichenberger, Arnold G., 1963-69 (Box 52, Folder 1460)
      Includes offprint of "The Cast of Lope's Los Benavides, 1968, inscribed to Wilder
    - Reinhardt, Helene, 1938-74 (Box 52, Folder 1461)
    - Reinhardt, Max, 1938-43, n.d. (Box 52, Folder 1462)
      With: letter to Wilder by Serge Bertensson, 1938
    - Reyman, Vernon, 1964-73 (Box 52, Folder 1463)
    - Richardson, Robert, 1963 (Box 52, Folder 1464)
      See also: Carol Stone, Box 48, folder 1589
    - Riegl, Kurt, 1964 (Box 52, Folder 1465)
    - Rigby Limited, 1962 (Box 52, Folder 1466)
    - Rives, Ralph Hardee, 1972-73 (Box 52, Folder 1467)
    - Robinson, Edwin Arlington, 1932 Feb 4 (Box 52, Folder 1468)
    - Roerich, Bill, 1963-75, n.d. (Box 53, Folder 1469)
      See also: Series II, Box 80, folder 2087a
    - Rogers, Bill, 1960-77 (Box 53, Folder 1470)
    - Rogers, Mildred
    - Rogers, Ginger, 1966 Oct 1 (Box 53, Folder 1471)
      With: letter to Wilder from Paul Beardsley, 1972
    - Roosevelt, Eleanor B., 1940, 1947 (Box 53, Folder 1472)
      With: invitation to Inaugural tea 1941
    - Root, Maggie, 1965-67 (Box 53, Folder 1473)
    - Rosalie Stewart Agency, 1934-65 (Box 53, Folder 1474-1476)
    - Rose, Francis, Sir, 1951-63, n.d. (Box 53, Folder 1477)
    - Rothenberg, Stanley
      See: Heit & Rothenberg, Box 41, folders 1039-1048
    - Rowse, A. L., 1966, n.d. (Box 53, Folder 1478)
    - Royal Academy of Dramatic Art
      See: Arthur Klein, Box 45, folder 1175
    - Rukeyser, Muriel, 1954 Feb 1 (Box 53, Folder 1479)
      With: signed typescript of "Exile of Music"
    - Russell, Helen, 1954-56, n.d. (Box 53, Folder 1480)
    - "S" general, 1930-75, n.d. (Box 53, Folder 1481-1489)
    - S4N Magazine
      See: Norman Fitts, Box 33, folder 835
    - S. Fischer Verlag, 1950-67 (Box 53, Folder 1490-91)
    - S. Fischer Verlag, 1968-75 (Box 54, Folder 1492)
    - Sabatelli, Louis, 1966 (Box 54, Folder 1493)
    - Sackville-West, Vita, 1928 Mar 7 (Box 54, Folder 1494)
    - Sahl, Hans, 1954-74, n.d. (Box 54, Folder 1495)
    - Saint-Denis, Michael, 1938-54 (Box 54, Folder 1496)
      With: letter to Wilder by Suria Saint-Denis, 1974
    - Saint-John Perse, 1941-50 (Box 54, Folder 1497)
    - Samuel French, Ltd., 1931-80 (Box 54, Folder 1498-1504)
      With: third-party correspondence concerning European production rights
    - Sanford, W. R., 1962-64 (Box 54, Folder 1505)
      With: copy of article by Sanford on Wilder's work
    - Sarason, Bertram, 1962-74 (Box 54, Folder 1506)
    - Sartre, Jean-Paul, 1946 (Box 54, Folder 1507)
      With: letter from Wilder to Miss Fishbein, 1946
    - Saturday Evening Post, 1962-63 (Box 54, Folder 1508)
    - Saturday Review of Literature, 1942-67 (Box 54, Folder 1509)
    - Saunders, Marion, 1948 (Box 54, Folder 1510)
    - Schauspielhaus Zurich, 1957-62 (Box 54, Folder 1511)
    - Schibler, Armin, 1972 Nov 10 (Box 54, Folder 1512)
    - Schiefflin, John Jay, 1962 (Box 54, Folder 1513)
    - Schlueter, Paul, 1971-72 (Box 54, Folder 1514)
    - Schneider, Alan, 1955-71 (Box 54, Folder 1515)
    - Schnitzer, Bob, 1961-75, n.d. (Box 54, Folder 1516-17)
    - Schnitzer, Marcella
    - Scholastic, 1957 (Box 55, Folder 1518)
    - Schönberg, Carolina, 1967-75, n.d. (Box 55, Folder 1519)
    - Schönberg, Lorimaria, 1968-74, n.d. (Box 55, Folder 1520)
    - Schorer, Mark, 1966-69 (Box 55, Folder 1521)
    - Schott, Regina, 1963-65 (Box 55, Folder 1522)
    - Schromm, Percy Ernst, 1966 Jun 8 (Box 55, Folder 1523)
    - Schwartz, Donald M., 1967-70 (Box 55, Folder 1524)
    - Scott, Foresman & Co., 1956 (Box 55, Folder 1525)
    - Scott, Martha, n.d. (Box 55, Folder 1526)
    - Scott, Winfield Townley, 1961-66 (Box 55, Folder 1527)
    - Scott, Eleanor
    - Schweitzer, Albert, 1955 Jun 5 (Box 55, Folder 1528)
      With: offprints, 1951, n.d.
    - Seagull Publishers, 1960 (Box 55, Folder 1529)
    - Sebastian, Fanny B., 1963 (Box 55, Folder 1530)
    - Seelye, Linda, 1967 (Box 55, Folder 1531)
    - Selby, David, 1965-66 (Box 55, Folder 1532)
    - Selby, Percival, 1943 (Box 55, Folder 1533)
    - Seldes, Marian, 1963-67 (Box 55, Folder 1534)
    - Senn, Fritz, 1961-73, n.d. (Box 55, Folder 1535)
      With: letter to Wilder from Beda Senn, n.d.
    - Sergeant, Elizabeth Shepley, 1938-62, n.d. (Box 55, Folder 1536)
    - Seven Bookhunters, 1952-65 (Box 55, Folder 1537)
    - Shaktman, Ben, 1966 (Box 56, Folder 1538)
    - Sheean, Vincent, 1956-75 (Box 56, Folder 1539-1547)
    - Sheean, Dinah
    - Sheldon, Ned, 1938, n.d. (Box 56, Folder 1548)
    - Shelton, Richard
      See: Ruth Stephan, Box 58, folder 1580
    - Shepherd, George, 1951-61, n.d. (Box 56, Folder 1549)
    - Shumlin, Herman, 1939 (Box 56, Folder 1550)
    - Simenon, Georges, 1954-68, n.d. (Box 56, Folder 1551)
    - Simenon, Denise
    - Simon & Schuster, 1962-72 (Box 56, Folder 1552)
    - Sitwell, Sacheverell, 1965, 1975 (Box 56, Folder 1553)
    - Sizer, Theodore, 1964-65 (Box 56, Folder 1554)
    - Skidmore College, 1966 (Box 56, Folder 1555)
    - Slocum, John J., 1949 Jun 21 (Box 56, Folder 1556)
      With: offprint of "Five More Pages of James Joyce's Stephen Hero, inscribed to Wilder and signed by Slocum and Herbert Cahoon, n.d.
    - Slusser, Dorothy, 1959 (Box 56, Folder 1557)
    - Smiley, Jos., 1943, n.d. (Box 56, Folder 1558)
    - Social Science Club, New Haven, 1963-65 (Box 56, Folder 1559)
    - Society of Authors, 1962 (Box 56, Folder 1560)
    - Society of Stage Directors and Choreographers, 1966 (Box 56, Folder 1561)
    - Solters, O'Rourke, & Sabinson, Inc., 1965-66 (Box 56, Folder 1562)
    - Spellman, Francis, 1940 Feb 21 (Box 56, Folder 1563)
    - Stainton, Laura del Bono, 1957-63 (Box 56, Folder 1564-1566)
    - Stainton, Neale
      With: third-party correspondence concerning Italian publication rights
    - Stallman, Robert, 1960-77 (Box 56, Folder 1567)
    - Stanford University, 1965-66 (Box 56, Folder 1568)
    - Stanton, Dorothy L., 1966 (Box 56, Folder 1569)
    - State University of New York at Albany, 1965 (Box 56, Folder 1570)
    - State University of New York at Buffalo, 1963 (Box 56, Folder 1571)
    - Stearns, Harold
      See: The Dial, Box 31, folder 773
    - Stein, Gertrude, 1934-41 (Box 57, Folder 1572-1577)
    - Copies of correspondence between Stein and Wilder, manuscript and typescript, 1935-39 (Box 57, Folder 1578)